Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
- Series IV. Ephemera
  - Subseries IVa. Press Kits, Band Publicity, Etc.
    - The Fast 5-leaf press packet with photograph, ca. 1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Haunch of Venison/Toby Mott folded poster, September-October, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - The Child Molesters pamphlet containing press clippings, ca. 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - The Hospital "Punk: A Trues and Dirty Tale" pamphlet, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - The Instant Automatons insert from 1980 cassette release, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Kriminella Gitarrer facsimile of 1979 press release, ca. 2001-2010 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Rock It Dirty Thirty Hit Record Survery No. 5, December 23, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Obituaries and articles on Peter Laughner, ca. 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art press kit for exhibit "Anglo Mania", 2006 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Max's Kansas City poster, menu (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - The New York Dolls press kit, 1974? (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The New York Dolls news release from Polydor, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The New York Dolls invitation at the Whisky A-Go-Go, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The New York Dolls invitation at the Hollywood Palladium, with VIP pass, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - The Ramones press release, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Rough Trade "Delta Five" press packet, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Rubber Dubber Records, 3 press items, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - The Screamers press packet, ca. 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - The Screamin Mee-Mees press release, 1977? (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sex Pistols press release, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Sex Pistols/Glitterbest letterhead, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - The Homosexuals press release, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - The Weirdos press kit and photograph, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Cameron, Dougie. "Sex Pistols" sale list of bootlegs, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - The Cartel "The Catalogue", 1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Gulcher Records set sale no. 4, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Mod. "The Sex Pistols Gear…" handbill (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Poseur catalog, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Poseur "For Punks and Mods", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - "Rock and Roll…Now! Sex Pistols are Swiss!!!" leaf, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Rough Trade "Distribution Catalogue", 1980 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Rough Trade "Secrets of the Unknown", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Sardine Productions catalog, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Small Distribution Company "Independent Cassettes and Zines", 1981 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Vinyl Fetish Catalog and leaf, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Zed Records catalog, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Zensor catalog in German, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Zigzag "Zigzag Cassette Book, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Signed flier, with The Worst, Manicured Noice, and the Negatives (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Sunday Life, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Sunday Matinee (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Ramones "At Least We Got Noticed" photocopied press release (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Jack Rabid photocopied Xmas shopping list, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous/Unknown (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous/Unknown (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Sex Pistols Contract (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - John Savage articles, etc. (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - The Ramones miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Swell Maps memorabelia (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - John Holstrom "Punk Magazine #5" drawing boards (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Subseries IVb. Photocopies
    - DIY Sleeves A: Acme Attractions-Astronauts (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - DIY Sleeves B: Balloons-Burns (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - DIY Sleeves C: Cabaret-Current Obsessions (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - DIY Sleeves D: Dave Bishop-Dry Ribs (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - DIY Sleeves E: Eskimo Vinyl-Eternal Scream (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - DIY Sleeves F: False Idols-Funboy Five (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - DIY Sleeves G: Glass-Grow Up (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - DIY Sleeves H: Homosexuals-Human Cabbages (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - DIY Sleeves I: Idol Death-IQ Zero (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - DIY Sleeves J: Jelly Babies (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - DIY Sleeves L: Last Thought-London PX (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - DIY Sleeves M: Manchester Mekon-Mud Hutters (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - DIY Sleeves N: Nancy Sesay-The Now (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - DIY Sleeves O: "O" Level-Outsize Oddments (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - DIY Sleeves P: Panic in the Year Zero-Puritans (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - DIY Sleeves R: Reacta-Rough Cuts (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - DIY Sleeves S: Sanna Brothers-Sunday Painters (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - DIY Sleeves T: Take It-Tronics (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - DIY Sleeves U: U-Turn (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - DIY Sleeves V: Vampire Dead-Vice Versa Music (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - DIY Sleeves W: Wasteland-Worms (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - DIY Sleeves Y: Young Marble Giants (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - DIY Sleeves Z: Zeitgeist (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 5 copies of Vintage Pictures (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 7 copies of fliers (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous clippings and fanzines (Box 9, Folder 9-11)
    - DIY Research (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - Subseries IVc. Miscellaneous
    - 107 vintage buttons for various UK bands and labels (Box 9, Folder 38-39)
    - "Here's your free punk pin…" coupon, 1977-1982 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - "News…news…news…" handbill, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Class War, 4 handbills, 1980s-1990s (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Loose page from "NYC Babylon: From Beat to Punk", page 151-152 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Sex pistols "Hot as a Sex Pistol" T-shirt transfer, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Sticker for the band Suicide (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - International Flamin' Groovies Fanclub. "Open Market" handbill (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Anti-bootleg flier from the WFMU Record Fair, ca. 2000's (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Photocopy of anti-sex pistols handbill (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Committee Against Racism photocopy of anti-punk handbill, ca. 1970s (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Loose leaf from unidentified fanzine, containing pictures of The Dose and an ad for Skrewdriver, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - "This Mindless Crap Promotes an Unthinking Ugly Society" stamp (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - "Sterile Vision" stamp (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - "Man made power, man made pain" stamp (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Digital Dinosaurs archive: music, lyrics, stickers, pamphlets, photographs (Box 28, Folder 8-10)
    - Digital Dinosaurs archive: music, lyrics, stickers, pamphlets, photographs (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Digital Dinosaurs archive: fliers (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Hand-written list, "I did you no wrong…" (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Series V. Manuscripts
  - Mock-up workfile for Punk: An Aesthetic., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 27-37)
  - Crabs archive (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Azzolesi, Joseph. TLS, 1 leaf, to “Editor” [Gloria Stavers]., 24-Mar-69 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - “Alastair.” 2 ALS, 2 pp., n.d., to “Dave,” on photocopied Sex Pistols letterhead. Based on the content of the letters, it is likely that Alastair was a fanzine editor. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Simon Eastman self interview (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Danny Fields, "Freak" typescript, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Photocopy of TLS from Rich Goldman to Doug Spellman (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Richard Hell, "You Gotta Lose" draft, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Jon Savage, "Punk Rock Five Years On: A Warning Sign?" drafts (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Jon Savage “Our Foreign Correspondent writes: Top show biz moguls and TV personalities were convicted last week...” typescript, ca 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Jon Savage “Face: 70s Fashion: All Aboard for Funtime.” (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Jon Savage TLS to Greg Shaw, September 12, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Jon Savage letter to Greg shaw, with 6 photocopies of Sex Pistols photographs and Jamie Reid art, ca 1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Schlossburg, Mark. ALS to Jon Savage, ca 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - “Sex Pistols Tapes Feb. 76/Jan. 78.” list of recordings, photocopy (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Skydog Press Release, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - M Taylor ALS to Bomp (Greg Shaw) (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Violent ALS to reviewers for Sounds, ca 1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Lars Wallin ALS to Johan Kugelberg, ca 1983 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Lars Wallin MS to Johan Kugelberg, ca 1983 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Mike Weldon transcript of interview by Jon Savage (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Frank Zappa, "Who are the Brain Police?" printed facsimile of sheet music, ca 1966 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Kugelburg T-Shirt book material
    - Miscellaneous research, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - T-shirt photographs, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Photographs and negatives, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 3-7)
    - Photo albums, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
    - Miscellaneous research and magazines, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
    - Prints in portfolio, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Prints from portfolio, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Prints from portfolio, 1, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Prints from portfolio, 2, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Prints from portfolio, 3, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Hard drive and charger, 2005-2006 (Box 23)
    - Prints from portfolio, 2005-2006 (Box 23)
  - Interview transcripts for England's Dreaming
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1987-11-26 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Ant, Adam
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-27 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      McDowell, Al
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1989-05-28 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Beverley, Anne
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-07-06 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Harwood, Barbara
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-16 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Berlin
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Green, Bob
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
      Coon, Caroline
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      Goodman, Dave
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
      Wilson, Debbi
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-05 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      Morris, Dennis
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
      Jarman, Derek
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
      Letts, Don
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
      Matlozk, Glen
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
      Wallington Lloyd, Helen
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1987-08-06 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      Reid, Jamie
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
      Casey, Jayne
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
      Stevens, Joe
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-30 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      Strummer, Joe
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-06-23 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      Holmstrom, John
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
      Lydon, John
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1990-01-11 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      Tiberi, John
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
      Ingham, John
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-03-09 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      Jordan
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
      Temple, Julien
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
      Miles Kingston, June
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
      Black Childers, Lee
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-06-26 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      McNeill, Legs
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-06 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      Linder
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 29)
      Garrett, Malcom
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1989-06-12 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      McLaren, Malcom
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 31)
      Pirroni, Marco
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 32)
      Perry, Mark
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-06-08 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      Havron, Mary
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1989-01-29 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      Morrissey
    - Interview by Jon Savage (Box 41, Folder 35)
      Stevenson, Nils
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-26 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      Cook, Paul
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-03-15 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      Murray, Pauline
    - Interview by Jon Savage (Box 41, Folder 38)
      Shelley, Pete
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-11-05 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      Hook, Peter
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 40)
      Stevenson, Ray
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 41)
      Boon, Richard
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 42)
      Roadent
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 43)
      Bayley, Roberta
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-03-25 (Box 41, Folder 44)
      Armstrong, Roger
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1990-09-21 (Box 41, Folder 45)
      Johnston, Rory
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1980-03-07 (Box 41, Folder 46)
      Hasler, Shanne
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-03-28 (Box 41, Folder 47)
      Barker, Simon
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-07-15 (Box 41, Folder 48)
      Sioux, Siouxsie
    - Interview by Jon Savage (Box 41, Folder 49)
      Richmond, Sophie
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1987-06-03 (Box 41, Folder 50)
      Jones, Steve
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-11-05 (Box 41, Folder 51)
      Severin, Steve
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 52)
      Walsh, Steve
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 53)
      Wilson, Tony
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-05 (Box 41, Folder 54)
      Smith, TV
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-06-20 (Box 41, Folder 55)
      Vale
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1988-05-25 (Box 41, Folder 56)
      Godard, Vic
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 57)
      Albertine, Viv
    - Interview by Jon Savage, 1987-12-10 (Box 41, Folder 58)
      Nightengale, Warwick
    - Interview by Jon Savage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 59)
      Wire
- Series VI. Artwork
  - Miscellaneous original artwork (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Emerson, Hunt. "The Sex Pistols" marker drawing, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Emerson, Hunt. "The Sex Pistols" color print, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Susanna Vida. "The Homosexuals" original flier art, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - "The Secrets Here at the Everyman Bistro", stencil and signed poster, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Jamie Reid "Underneath Lurking…" original watercolor (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Jamie Reid "Proletariat learn your strength…"Original print signed (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Harry North and Larry Seigel, "Mad's Punk Rock Group of the year" artwork, 4 pages, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Jaime Reid surrealist painting (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Jamie Reid prints and paintings, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Jamie Reid prints and paintings (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Ray Stevenson "Sex Pistols File" (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Susanna Vida "Homosexuals" color print, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Savage Pencil "Santa Dog", 1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - The Litter. "Distortions" proof (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Jamie Reid and Jon Savage. Paste up from "Up they Rise", 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Punk RMC exhibit posters, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - DNA cover art and mechanicals for the single "You and You" (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Peter Laughner "Space Age Thrills", 1972 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Jaime Hernandez "Hey! We're talking to you!" PSA, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Generation X original paste up (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Series VII. Photographs
  - Lester Bangs on stage, likely performing with the Delinquents or Birdland, ca 1970s (Box 28, Folder 48)
    Photographer: Mykel Board
  - Black Flag, black and white print of Black Flag’s early lineup, ca. 1976-1979. Print made ca. 2004-2010., ca. 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Black Flag, vintage color print of Henry Rollins performing with Black Flag in Sweden, ca. 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Photographer: Johann Kugelberg
  - Clash/101ers, color inkjet print of the 101ers (Joe Strummer’s pre-Clash pub rock band) performing onstage (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Richard Hell, vintage color photocopy (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Photographer: Roberta Bayley
  - The Monks, from the 1997 Infinite Zero/American Recordings reissue of Black Monk Time., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - New York Dolls seated at a bust stop, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Photographer: Bob Gruen
  - New York Dolls on stage, two prints (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Pere Ubu/Rocket from the Tombs, vintage black and white print of David Thomas and Peter Laughner in conversation, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Punk Magazine founders: Jed Dunn, Legs McNeil, John Holmstrom, CBGB NYC, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Rocket From the Tombs, two black and white prints, ca 1975 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Photographer: Fred Toedtman
  - Sex Pistols and circle, 9 photocopies, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    Photographer: Various
  - Sex Pistols shooting "Pretty Vacant" video, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sex Pistols, Sid Vicious surrounded by "God Save the Queen" merchandise, ca. 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Photographer: John Tiberi
  - Sex Pistols, vintage color print of Soo Catwoman, ca. 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sex Pistols, color print of a still from the unfinished film Who Killed Bambi?, showing a dead deer. (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sex Pistols, Two vintage black and white promotional prints bearing the logos of the Sex Pistols and EMI. One shows the band (with Glen Matlock), the other shows Steve Jones alone. (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Sex Pistols, two prints. One shows Johnny Rotten in a plane (over Sweden) the other shows the band standing at the top of stairs leading to the top of an embankment. (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - The Survivors (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Photographer: Tom Hearn
  - Dead Boys, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Photographer: Godlis
  - Ramones, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Unknown (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Sire Records, mounted color prints from contest, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Jonathan Richman performing (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Photographer: Richard McCaffrey
- Series VIII. Audio
  - Messthetics 106, 108, 110, 207, 209 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Series IX. Clothing
  - Vivienne Westwood and Malcolm McLaren T-shirts (Box 32)
  - Vivienne Westwood and Malcolm McLaren necktie (Box 32)
  - Bad Brains T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Beserkely Records T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Butthole Surfers T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Buzzcocks T-shirts (Box 32)
  - Elvis Costello T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Elvis Costello and the Attractions T-shirts (Box 32)
  - Dead Boys T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Modern Lovers T-shirt (Box 32)
  - MX-80 Sound T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Psychic TV T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Punk Magazine/Lou Reed T-shirt (Box 32)
  - The Residents T-shirts (Box 32)
  - Sex Pistols T-shirts (Box 32)
  - Sex Pistols cloth banner (Box 32)
  - Sire Records T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Throbbing Gristle T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Tuxedomoon T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Wiseblood T-shirt (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous T-shirts (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous T-shirts (Box 35)